The Land of Truth Tellers?
But on the map, it says--
It changed to that name six months ago.
As the name says, it has
become a country with no liars.
Huh.
Once you enter our territory,
even if you're a witch,
your body will not be able to lie.
Why in the world did this happen?
It's because of the mysterious
power of the sword the king has.
Sword?
With the power of his sword brimming with magic,
he has put up a barrier around the whole
country to keep those within from lying.
That seems kind of shady.
Madam Witch, you are already being honest.
Actually, I agree with you.
Well, what will you do?
Will you enter the country?
Well...
I'm still of two minds, and still suspicious,
but it sounds like it'll make
a good story, so I'll try going in.
You are honest.
Welcome to the Land of Truth Tellers!
Welcome to this damned country!
"The Land of Truth Tellers"
The Land of Truth Tellers, huh?
It looks like a normal town, though.
For now, I'll test whether or not I can lie.
I'll try saying "I am not beautiful."
I am not beauti--beauti--
I am very beautiful!
Oh, my mouth moved on its own to tell the truth!
It looks like what they said
about not being able to lie was true.
Be that as it may,
it's kind of quiet around here.
I wonder why no one's talking...
Those look good.
Are these freshly baked?
Then, I'll take one, please.
So hard... What's with this?
It's hard and dry. It's probably
unsold bread leftover from yesterday.
She made it sound like
it was freshly baked, though.
What's so honest about this country anyway?
Since they said there are
only honest people here,
I was imagining that the people
would be more pure, somehow.
Looks like I was wrong, though.
Instead, they seem kind of distant,
and things seem kind of tense.
I wonder what made the king
decide to change the country like this.
"You're the witch dispatched from
the United Magic Association, right?"
No, that's not me.
To put it simply, the United Magic
Association is a mysterious organization
that meddles in everything
that deals with magic.
Those affiliated with the association
have a brooch shaped like a moon.
What was that about?
Hm? What about if it's written down?
Is it still not possible to lie?
"New sweets! Actually, we just added
some new things to old products."
"A mystery woven by a new author!
Even that bestselling author
was shocked by how boring it was!"
Hm, let's see...
I'll try writing "I have a twisted
personality" and see what happens.
"I have a pure heart."
I see. You can't even lie through writing.
What the hell?
You're so stubborn!
You're pigheaded, too!
You scheming bastard! You should just die!
You bellyacher! You should die!
--What did you say?! I can't believe you
went after a woman so out of your league!
--Oh my, just when I finally heard some
voices, it turns out it was an argument.
--What did you say?! I can't believe you
went after a woman so out of your league!
--Oh my, just when I finally heard some
voices, it turns out it was an argument.
--Yeah, I was sure she liked me.
Um, is it all right to let them go on like that?
It helps us release stress, too.
In fact, I wish they'd do it more.
Oh, is that how it is?
Why won't the people in this country talk?
Because if we talk,
since we can only tell the truth,
we'll end up fighting like that, of course.
Miss Witch, are you an idiot?
See? All of this is that stupid king's fault.
Whoops.
Okay, stop right there!
Can you please not have
a fist fight in broad daylight?
Why didn't any of you stop...
...them?
Miss Elaina!
Oh. I'm sorry!
I didn't think I'd see you here!
Is this fate? It is, isn't it?
We have no choice but to get married, right?
Putting that aside, it's been
a long time, hasn't it, Saya?
I'm glad you seem to be well.
Thanks to this hat...
...and this treasure...
...I'm doing very well!
That's my...
I was able to become a witch, too!
I see. Congratulations.
What's your witch title?
The Charcoal Witch!
Charcoal, huh? It's a little
like my "Ashen Witch."
Of course.
Because I asked my teacher
to choose a word close to "ashen."
I see.
Are you part of the United Magic Association?
I thought it was the easiest way
to make money as I traveled.
I'm in this country for work, too!
Work?
Yes!
I bought something a little pricey,
so I need to work a lot...
Speaking of which,
I met someone earlier who was
looking for a witch from the association.
Oh, what did they look like?
I didn't get a name or address in the request...
You incompetent witch! You're back again?!
Hurry up and get out of here!
"Eek! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!"
Don't tell me it's that
weird person over there...
It's that weird person.
Do you think you could let go of me now?
No, that's all right.
Um... You were looking for a witch
dispatched by the association, right?
Let me introduce you to my friend, Saya.
"Friend" sounds so formal here.
Oh, hello.
"Sorry. I was in a hurry, so I forgot
to write my name and address."
Eihemia, is it that you can't talk,
or that you won't talk?
Which is it?
"I lost my voice because of certain reasons."
Are you going to write all the reasons?
Oh, this looks like it'll take a while.
Saya...
Eihemia then told us about those reasons--
No, she wrote them. From what she wrote--
About six months ago,
Eihemia, a witch who worked in the palace,
received a request from the king.
Quicksand Witch, Eihemia,
please use your power to get
rid of all the liars in this country.
Huh?
All my retainers are liars.
I only want people near me who
will say what they really think.
What should I do...?
If I can help the king, then maybe...
No way...
I know.
I just have to put up a barrier
that won't let people lie.
Eihemia found a suitable sword in the castle
and tried to make it a vessel
for the magic of the barrier.
All right.
Ianesana-ha, ianesana-ha...
Ominano motera-do!
But she needed a large amount
of magic to perform the spell.
--Eihemia poured in all her magic,
--Ominano motera-do!
but that wasn't enough,
so she even gave up her voice
to complete the barrier sword.
I wonder why people who
are trying to accomplish things
end up giving up their voices
or memories in exchange...
Huh?
Nothing, just talking to myself.
Oh? A barrier sword?
So you're saying that if
I hold this in my dominant hand,
I can put up a barrier that will prevent
people from lying in this country?
A land of truth tellers, huh? Not bad.
But man, this sword is really lame.
It's so gaudy.
Even though it's to put up the barrier,
I can't believe I have
to hold a sword like this...
And so, the Land of Truth Tellers was born.
By the way, since Eihemia
couldn't use magic anymore,
she was thrown out of the palace
because she was now incompetent.
"I didn't have any worth other than my magic..."
You were hired as a witch,
so of course you would be
valued mostly for your magic.
"Even so, I'd been hoping that
he would still keep me by his side."
Knowing that you gave up all
your magic and even your voice
could be overwhelming, right?
Don't you think that's what put off the king?
So, your request is to put this country
back to what it was before, right?
What should I do to put it back?
"Just destroy the king's sword. Then, my magic
and voice will return to normal, too."
I see.
Should I aim for when the king
comes out of the castle or something?
"He will make a speech in one month."
Miss Elaina! Let's stay in
the same room for one month
and eat and sleep together!
Oh, and bathe together, and we might
as well go to the bathroom together,
and sleep in the same bed--
Let's come up with a different plan.
"Going into the palace might be the best bet."
But if we can't lie, don't you
think it would be hard to get in?
It doesn't look like we can get in from the sky,
and security looks tight...
It's the Land of Truth Tellers,
so it'd be hard to get in by lying.
But.
But?
We can use that and make it work somehow.
Somehow?
A picture is worth a thousand words.
What business do you have?
You may not enter the palace
without permission from the king.
You're back again?
You've been banished from here!
Come on, Saya, please explain the situation.
Very well.
Ahem. Mr. Doorman, do you
understand what is written here?
"The banishment
of the witch, Eihemia,
has been revoked,
and she is to enter the palace
with Elaina, the Ashen Witch,
and Saya, the Charcoal Witch.
We have the permission
of the king"? What?!
Really?
This is the Land of Truth Tellers, right?
We can't lie, can we?
Well, that's true...
May we enter?
Oh, that worked! As expected of Miss Elaina.
It wasn't much.
It was simple.
We just had to write
the sentences down in chunks.
Since none of the parts contained
any lies, they could be written down.
Then, they just had to
be read in the right order,
and we could write anything we wanted.
The pen really is mightier than the sword, huh?
I'm not sure about that, though.
Eihemia, where's the throne room?
There?
Oh, could you be the king?
Yes, I am.
Please let go of that sword.
If you don't...
Intruders!
What? There are three witches!
One of them's Eihemia!
Long time no see!
Man, this is such a pain, and I'm sleepy.
That witch has a flat chest,
but she's pretty cute!
The boyish witch over here's my type!
Oh, sorry, I already have
my heart set on someone.
Please don't look at me.
Saya, I will take the king.
Please do something about the guards.
Leave it to me, Saya, the Charcoal Witch!
"I am a non-combatant."
Please hand over the sword.
What are you saying?
This sword is the greatest weapon,
made to guide this country.
As long as I have this, I can lead
this country in the correct direction.
There's no way I'd hand it over!
Sorry.
So mean...
"That sword can release stored
magic, so please be careful."
"It'll hurt a lot if it hits you."
Please tell us that first next time!
Damn it!
Did getting rid of lies
make this country any better?
Of course it did!
Is that really true?
What?!
People with evil intent can
do evil things without lying.
Just because this country
became full of truth tellers
doesn't mean that everyone in
this country became a good person.
And not all liars are evil.
Sometimes white lies can act as lubricant
to smooth over relationships between people.
Without that, people just grate on
each other's nerves and become tense.
That's not true!
If the sword is the truth,
then lies are the scabbard (saya).
Yes?
I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking about a sword scabbard.
Well, that's confusing!
What is?
If the sword is truth, then lies
are the scabbard for that sword.
To keep us from swinging the truth
around recklessly and hurting people,
the truth is wrapped in lies.
You little... Babbling on like that...
Miss Elaina!
There are too many enemies!
I can't take care of them all.
I feel like my brain's going to explode!
"Do your best!"
Well, it looks like Saya is at her limit, too,
so let's end this.
End this?
Haven't you had to use everything
you've got just to hold back my attacks?
No, I'm sorry.
I've already been prepared
to take that sword from you
for a long time.
The really lame sword!
You did it, Miss Elaina!
Are you saying... that I was wrong?
No, Your Majesty.
Eihemia...
Your desire to be honest is not wrong.
But from now on, why don't you relax a little...
...and lie and be lied to as
you govern this land... okay?
Fresh bread!
Do you want some fresh fish?
You really are a good guy, huh?
And you've really got some guts!
The king recognized his own mistake
and apologized to the country's citizens
for making it so they couldn't lie.
I don't know if the country
will go back to how it was,
but Eihemia is back at the palace,
so I'm sure it'll all work out, somehow.
Madam Witches, thank you very much!
Have a safe trip!
Um, the association's rules state
that I must give you a present
to thank you for your help.
Huh? I don't need anything.
If you do everything by the book,
then you'll become inflexible.
But please let me thank you!
It's nothing big, but--
Ta-da!
A necklace?
I bought this with all the money I had
on hand to give you when I saw you again.
I took this job because I'd run out of money,
but that's how I got to see
you again, so it must be fate!
Please think of it as me and treasure it!
Huh? Your feelings are overwhelming.
But, thank you very much.
I'll put it on for you.
Huh? Wait.
Don't hold back.
It looks good on you!
Now we match!
Well, I need to head to
the association branch office.
Where will you go?
I'm heading to another unknown town somewhere.
It's a promise charm that
is used in my homeland.
Please hook your pinky in mine.
Let's meet again someday.
I want to introduce you to my sister,
and I'll be a better witch by then, too!
I promise!
Yes, I'll wait patiently as I travel.
I promise.